

Neymar John

Senior Web & Mobile App Developer



Contact

E-mail

neymarjohn215@gmail.com



Skills

Coding understanding

Excellent

Blockchain

••••

Excellent

React

••••

Excellent

Angular

••••

Excellent

Excellent

Vue

••••

Frontend

••••

Excellent

Node(Express)

••••

Excellent

Backend

Excellent

Ruby on Rails

Excellent

PHP(Laravel, CI, Wordpress)

••••

Excellent

Excellent

Mobile APP(React Native, IOS, Android, Ionic)

Java(Spring, Spring boot)

(4)

Professional Summary

I am honored to be here to show you about my skills and experiences. My destination is to become the top ranked Web Developer. My customers'order is just law for me. Skills: Blockchain, Web3, Solidity, Solana, NFT, Smart contract, Javascript, React, Angular, Vue, Node, Express, SQL, NoSQL, PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, AJAX, Javascript, SQL, XML, API Integration. I will always do my best to satisfy your demands and I feel great when I see my customer's satisfaction. I do care about all customers who want to make Websites. Everyday I am waiting for good Client in this platform. I will do my best for the beautiful life and dreams of this world.



Work History

2022-01 -Current

Senior Frontend and Backend Developer

Rafik, London, United Kingdom

This job is for mobile app version.

At first he asked only mobile version and I made it with React native.

He was satisfied with my working result and he implemented web version.

I finished only 5 days about web version and he was very happy.

2021-05 -Current

Full Stack Development

Marco designies, Krizevci, Croatia

This job is for full stack developer.

In this job he asked web and mobile app development At that time I was very interested in this job format and he tested my skills. So this project is booking system and I finished this app with Laravel for web.

Also now I am developing the mobile version and I am building with React native.

He is very happy with my work and I do my best for him. Croatia is tourism country and he wanted super app from me.

Now he made many client with this app.



Education

2011-04 -2015-02 **Associate of Science: Computer Science**

Kyiv National Taras Shevchenko University - Ukraine